(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(用外语)
(speaking in foreign language)
(引擎的转速)
(engine revving)
♬奇异的优雅♬
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♬这声音多么甜美
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
♬这救了我这样的可怜虫
♪ That saved a wretch like me ♪
(用外语)
(speaking in foreign language)
♪我曾经迷失♪
♪ I once was lost ♪
-我会一直读给你听
- I'm gonna keep reading this to you,
不仅因为这个故事对我意义重大，
and not just because the story means a lot to me,
而是因为我知道这对你很重要
but because I know it means a lot to you.
♬现在这个世界需要什么呢
♪ What the world needs now ♪
否则你不会把它写下来。
Else wise you wouldn't have wrote it down.
“1月21日，晚上11:45。”
"January 21st, 11:45 PM."
“我开车回家的时候给她打了电话。”
"I called her as I drove home."
-[语音信箱]你好，我是贝基。
- [Voicemail] Hey there, this is Becky.
我现在不在这里
I'm not here right now,
但我等不及要听你为我准备的消息了
but I can't wait to hear what you have for me.
(机器哔哔)
(machine beeping)
——嘿,宝贝。
- Hey babe.
所以,
So,
我真的告诉他了。
I actually told him.
你会很自豪的。
You would've been so proud.
我告诉他们"你得找到"
I told them "You're gonna have to find"
“今晚有人替我吗?”
"someone to cover me tonight"
"这周剩下的每个晚上"
"and every night for the rest of the week"
“或者直到项目完成。”
"or until the project's done."
我得说，那感觉很解放。
And I gotta say, it felt liberating.
我真的觉得自己正在好转。
I really feel like I'm turning a corner.
总之，我在回家的路上，
Anyway um, I'm on my way home and uh,
我有一瓶你喜欢的那种，
I got a bottle of that kind you like,
我们很快就会再见的。
and uh, I'll see you soon.
我爱你，宝贝。
I love you, babe.
♪到时间的尽头♪
♪ To the end of time ♪
♬现在这个世界需要什么呢
♪ What the world needs now ♪
(贝基尖叫)是爱，甜蜜的爱
(Becky squealing) ♪ Is love, sweet sweet love ♪
♪这是唯一的。♪实在太少了
♪ It's the only thing that's there's just too little of ♪
-我操!
- [Becky] Oh, fuck me!
(贝基尖叫)(男人嘟囔着)
(Becky screams) (man grunting)
-他就这样干你?
- [Man] He fuck you like this?
-天哪!
- [Becky] God no!
哦,上帝!
Oh God!
(贝基尖叫)不，不是只有一些♬
(Becky screaming) ♪ No not just for some ♪
♪但是为了每个人，为了每个人
♪ But for everyone, for everyone ♪
主啊，我们不需要另一片草地
♪ Lord we don't need another meadow ♪
♪这里有足够的玉米地和麦田♪
♪ There are corn fields and wheat fields enough to grow ♪
♬有阳光也有月光
♪ There are sunbeams and moonbeams ♪
(贝基尖叫)♬足够亮♬
(Becky screaming) ♪ Enough to shine ♪
哦，听着，主啊，如果你想知道的话
♪ Oh listen, Lord, if you want to know ♪
♬现在这个世界需要什么呢
♪ What the world needs now ♪
-“安静，孩子，没事的。”
- "Hush now child, it's gon' be okay."
-[护士]你在看什么书?
- [Nurse] What's that you're reading?
——一个杂志。
- A journal.
他们找到他的时候就带着。
It was with him when they found him.
-这不是证据吗?
- Ain't that called evidence?
-这叫私人物品。
- It's called personal belongings.
-为什么给他读书?
- Why read to him?
他不是应该在昏迷中脑死亡吗?
Ain't he supposed to be brain dead on some kind of coma?
听不到你说话。
Can't even hear ya.
-我在乎也没办法
- Can't help that I care.
我看的时候，他的眼睛会眨一下。
His eyes sort of blink when I do.
让他脚踏实地。
Keeps him grounded to something.
至少我是这么想的。
That's what I think, at least.
-你为什么不直接动手呢
- Why don't you just lay your hands on him
做你说你能做的事。
and do that stuff you say you can do.
我是说，如果你真的有千里眼的话。
I mean, if you're a real clairvoyant and all.
-中号，我是中号
- Medium, I'm a medium.
我向你保证，如果这是上帝的意愿
And I assure you that if it's God's will
他碰巧过世了，
that he should happen to pass,
我来动手，我们好好谈谈。
I will lay hands and we'll have a conversation.
一个私人。
A private one.
我会告诉他，我感激生活
And I will tell him that I appreciate the life
爱他的生活。
and love that he's lived.
现在，如果你不介意的话
Now, if you'll excuse us.
-你做你自己，甜心。
- You do you, sugar.
我想抽根烟休息一下。
I'm a take a smoke break.
-“周一晚上，第一晚，真他妈糟糕。”
- "Monday night, first night, hell of a night."
"当我凝视她的那一刻"
"The second my eyes locked on her,"
“内心有一种强大而疯狂的东西在滴答作响。”
"something powerful crazy inside clicked."
“她是我生命所需的良药。”
"She was the medicine my life needed."
“这是难以形容的。”
"It was indescribable."
毫米。(笑)
Mm. (chuckles)
♬在你耳边小声说点什么♬
♪ Whispered something in your ear ♪
♬这么说太变态了
♪ It was a perverted thing to say ♪
♬但我还是说了♬
♪ But I said it anyway ♪
(光嗡嗡声)
(light buzzing)
♪让你笑了笑，把目光移开♪
♪ Made you smile and look away ♪
♬没有什么能伤害你，宝贝
♪ Nothing's gonna hurt you baby ♪
♪只要你和我在一起你就会没事
♪ As long as you're with me you'll be just fine ♪
♬没有什么能伤害你，宝贝
♪ Nothing's gonna hurt you baby ♪
♬没有什么能把你从我身边带走
♪ Nothing's gonna take you from my side ♪
-想上她?
- Thinking about fucking her?
——什么?
- What?
哦,不,不。
Uh, no, no.
我嗯,
I was um,
我，我，我只是，呃，只是
I, I, I was just uh, was just-
-如果你没有的话，你的裤管一定有问题。
- Something's wrong with your trouser worm if you weren't.
在去。
Go on in.
能告诉你想要-
Can tell you wanna-
-不，我只是，只是路过。
- No, I'm just uh, just, just passing through.
-是啊，你要去哪?
- Oh yeah, where are you headed?
-就是，你知道，呃，走开。
- Just, you know, um, away.
-是的。
- Yeah.
我已经朝那个方向走了一段时间了。
I've been headed that way for a while now.
只是不要出现在谷歌地图上，不是吗?
Just don't come up on Google Maps though, does it?
-不，没有。
- No, it don't.
-至少知道方向吧?
- Know a direction at least?
——西方。
- West.
♬没有什么能伤害你，宝贝
♪ Nothing's gonna hurt you baby ♪
你看过《末路狂花》吗?
You ever see "Thelma & Louise?"
——不。
- Nope.
为什么，好吃吗?
Why, is it good?
-还不错。
- It, it's not bad.
(弗兰克口吃)
(Frank stuttering)
他们开到尽头有条路，
There's a road they drive down at the end, I,
我想开车沿着那条路走。
I'd like to drive down that road.
-那条路漂亮吗?
- Is that road pretty?
-希望如此。
- I hope so.
-你喜欢漂亮，对吧?
- So you like pretty, huh?
那我想你应该见见佩内洛普。
Then I think you need to meet Penelope.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
-只有弗兰克，但我，我，我没时间
- Just Frank, but I, I, I don't have time.
——嘘。
- Shh.
请进，弗兰克。
Come on in, Just Frank.
我想她会喜欢你的。
I think she's gonna like you.
来吧。
Come on.
(监控哔哔声)
(monitor beeping)
-没事的，亲爱的。
- It's okay, sweetie.
你想让我继续读下去吗?
You want me to keep reading?
好的,我会的。
Okay, I will.
"知道我的日记真尴尬"
"Embarrassed of my journal to even know"
“我以前从没来过这些俱乐部，”
"that I'd never been in one of these clubs before,"
“但我的天，她真是美得惊人。”
"but my God, she was just breathtakingly beautiful."
(平静的音乐)
(calming music)
♬我12岁的时候就在跳舞
♪ I was dancing when I was 12 ♪
♬我出去的时候在跳舞
♪ I was dancing when I was out ♪
- 2:15，我们结束吧，好吗?
- 2:15, let's wrap it up, huh?
最后的一舞。
Last dance.
♬我一直从子宫里跳出来
♪ I danced myself right out the womb ♪
-想请我喝一杯吗?
- Wanna buy me this drink?
-是的，当然。
- Yeah uh, sure.
——这是25。
- It's 25.
——美元吗?
- Dollars?
-那又不是钱，宝贝
- Well, it ain't cents, baby.
♬我一直从子宫里跳出来
♪ I danced myself right out the womb ♪
♬我八岁的时候就在跳舞
♪ I was dancing when I was eight ♪
——好吗?
- Well?
——什么?
- Well what?
-你得把桌子挪开
- Well, you're gonna have to move the table out of the way
如果你想让我坐在你腿上。
if you want me to sit in your lap.
♬这么晚还跳舞，是不是很奇怪
♪ Is it strange to dance so late ♪
-现在你该对我撒谎了
- Now's when you lie to me
告诉我你会怎么干我。
and tell me all the ways that you'd fuck me.
让我癫痫发作，浑身是汗。
Leave me in an epileptic twitch and pool of sweat.
♬我跳着自己走进了坟墓
♪ I danced myself into the tomb ♪
继续，就弗兰克。
Go on, Just Frank.
告诉我，你到底要怎么上我?
Tell me, how exactly would you fuck me?
♬这么快就跳舞，是不是很奇怪
♪ Is it strange to dance so soon ♪
-很可能是公然无视你的快乐。
- Most likely with a blatant disregard for your pleasure.
——哦。
- Oh.
这要么是非常诚实，要么是非常自私。
Well, that's either incredibly honest or incredibly selfish.
-只是我
- It's just that I,
我从没遇到过像你这么漂亮的女朋友，
I never had a girlfriend as beautiful as you,
所以我觉得我撑不了多久
so I don't think I could last long enough
为了那些抽动的汗水。
for all that twitching sweat stuff.
我是说，如果我诚实的话
I mean, if I'm being honest,
这似乎是个自私的好机会。
it seemed like a really good opportunity to be selfish.
你能把第一部分再告诉我一遍吗?
- Can you tell me that first part again?
-我只知道我不是，我不是-
- I just know I'm not, I'm not-
-不不不
- No, no, no.
关于再做一次的部分，
The part about doing it again,
还有你从未有过的女朋友。
and girlfriends and the kind you ain't ever had.
-我只是说如果你想眨眼的话
- I'm just saying if you were wanting to blink
不要错过它，
and not miss it,
我们得做几次，
we'd have to do it a few times,
因为我已经准备好了…
'cause I'm all ready...
你知道,嗯,
You know, um-
——嘘。
- Shh.
你想做几次吗，弗兰克?
Do you wanna do it a few times, Frank?
-妈的，姑娘。
- Oh, God damn, girl.
你不知道。
You have no idea.
但我，我不想给你带来任何麻烦。
But I, I don't want to get you in any kind of trouble.
-所以你要走的那条路
- So that road you're going to,
你想去吗?
one you wanna go down?
你有把猎枪放在副驾驶位置吗?
You got a shotgun for that passenger seat?
我猜你已经有一个了，不是吗?
Oh, I guess you already got one though, don't you?
-不，我没有。
- No, I don't.
我45分钟前跟丢了。
I lost her about 45 minutes ago.
可能几年前就丢了。
Actually probably lost her years ago.
我45分钟前碰巧看到的。
I just happened to see it 45 minutes ago.
-你看到了什么，弗兰克?
- What'd you see, Frank?
-我老婆被干了
- My wife getting fucked
一个长得很像她综合健身教练的家伙。
by some dude who looked a lot like her CrossFit instructor.
哦宝贝。
- Oh baby.
你揍了他一顿?
You kick his fucking ass?
我打赌你说过。
I bet you did.
——没有。
- No.
——不是吗?
- No?
那说明你没有恋爱。
Well, then it means you ain't in love.
如果一个人没有大发雷霆，
If a man don't fly into a fit of rage,
这说明他没有恋爱。
it means he ain't in love.
-还给了她一枚传家宝戒指。
- Gave her an heirloom ring, too.
它一直握在我家每个孩子的手上
It's been on the hand that held every child in my family
五代。
for five generations.
从来没穿过它。
Never even wore it.
说石头太小了。
Said the stone was too small.
-那个脏婊子。
- Dirty bitch right there.
你打算怎么处理这枚戒指?
So what are you gonna do with this ring?
-扔远点。
- Throw it away, far away.
-需要帮忙吗?
- You need some help?
(佩内洛普·呻吟)
(Penelope moaning)
♬可能会死得太早
♪ Might die way too young ♪
只有这样我才能和你一起去旅行
Hey, the only way I'm gonna shotgun with you on that trip
如果你能把它永久扔掉。
is if you make that throw away permanent.
明白吗?
Okay?
——你说得对。
- You're right.
操她。
Fuck her.
我要把它卖掉，明天。
I'm gonna sell it, tomorrow.
-是吗?
- Are ya now?
去你的，小子
God damn you, boy,
你让我比庞恰特雷恩还湿。
you make me wetter than the Pontchartrain.
(佩内洛普·叹息)
(Penelope sighs)
——嘿!
- Hey!
看手。
Watch the hands.
你明白了吗?
You got it?
他妈的猫咪。
Fuckin' pussy.
-那你想让我怎么做，弗兰克?
- So what do you want me to do Frank?
——什么?
- About what?
-关于副驾驶的事
- About that shotgun seat.
你真的想让我加入吗?
You for real want me in it or not?
你认真的吗?
- You serious?
-嗯嗯。
- Mm-hm.
-你会离开这里和我一起去别的地方吗?
- You'd leave here and go somewhere with me?
——是的。
- Yes.
——为什么?
- Why?
哦,为什么是我?
Uh, why me?
-因为我的脑子里有一条断层
- 'Cause I got a fault line running through my head
我一次都没感觉到它变了
and I ain't felt it shift once
从你走到外面那扇门开始。
since you walked up to that door outside.
——大便。
- Shit.
我有点害怕。
I'm kind of scared of that.
同时也被它吸引。
And, and attracted to it at the same time.
-那个座位怎么样?
- So what about that seat?
嗯?
Huh?
-是的。——没有。
- Yeah. - No.
-是的,当然。
- Yeah, sure.
-不，那没用的
- No, that's not gonna work.
你得问我。
You have to ask me.
问我的。
Ask me proper.
告诉我你为什么不让我离开。
And tell me why you ain't gonna leave me nowhere.
因为你自己说过，第一次在我心里
'Cause you said it yourself, first time inside me,
你不会失去控制的。
you ain't gonna have no control.
但是第十次呢
But what about the 10th time
当你有足够的控制力的时候?
when you have plenty of control?
我怎么知道你不会离开我
How do I know you're not gonna leave me
在路边或者类似的地方吗?
on the side of the road or anything like that?
-因为我不是。
- 'Cause I'm not.
我生命中的每一个决定都是基于逻辑和理性做出的。
I made every decision in my life based on logic and reason.
我慢慢地权衡利弊。
I took my time, weighing out the pros and cons.
我有很多梦想，但我从来没有追求过一个。
I had a ton of dreams but I ain't never chased a single one.
也许我。
Maybe I'm due.
也许这场疯狂的追逐该轮到我了。
Maybe I'm due for that crazy chase.
尤其是那个“内洛普”
Especially for that 'Nelope
那是在外面的工作服里。
that was outside in them overalls.
我可能永远抓不到她，但是
I might never catch her, but,
去他的，我会尽力的。
fuck it, I'll do my best.
——哦。
- Oh.
-你愿意和我一起去吗?
- Will you come with me?
(佩内洛普·轻轻哭泣)
(Penelope crying lightly)
♪为什么你，为什么你，为什么你撒谎
♪ Why do you, why do you, why do you lie ♪
佩内洛普,
Penelope,
什么,怎么了?
what, what's wrong?
-我可以爱上你，弗兰克。
- I could fall in love with you, Frank.
我知道它。
I know it.
因为我在书上读到过
'Cause I read about it in books.
是的。
Yeah.
好，我和你一起去。
Yeah I'll go with you.
——佩内洛普!
- Penelope!
现在就在办公室。
In the office now.
-拜托告诉我那不是你男朋友
- Oh please tell me that's not your boyfriend.
耶稣·克莱斯勒，是吗?
Well Jesus Chrysler, is he?
-那混蛋以为他是。
- Asshole thinks he is.
-那混蛋说的对吗?
- Well is the asshole right?
- 45分钟前他还在
- Well he was right up until about 45 minutes ago,
但我要去拿我的东西了，好吗?
but I'm gonna go get my stuff, okay?
♬时间也在慢慢流逝
♪ And time was winding down ♪
你不会临阵脱逃吧，弗兰克?
You're not gonna chicken out on me, are you, Frank?
像其他人一样?
Like everybody else does?
-我不是其他人。
- I ain't everybody else.
快点。
Hurry up.
♬时间也在慢慢流逝
♪ And time was winding down ♪
-明白了吗?
- You get it?
-是的，我知道。
- Yeah, I got.
(人吸食)
(man snorting)
这里。
Here.
运行1000。
Just run it for 1,000.
50/50分。
50/50 split each.
他已经结婚了，所以他不会参加比赛。
He's married, so he's not gonna contest.
只要确保我不在片场就行
Just make sure I'm gone from the lot
在你把他赶出去之前
before you kick him out.
-五五分，去你的。
- 50/50 split, fuck you.
你得到正常的20%。
You get you normal 20%.
你什么时候开始亲嫖客了?
And since when do you kiss a John?
-他不是嫖客，你个混蛋。
- He's not a John, you fucking asshole.
我没上他。
I didn't fuck him.
-看起来你是想上他
- Well, it looked like you were trying to fuck him,
不是吗?
didn't it?
-是啊，我不得不亲他
- Yeah, well I had to kiss him
就为了拿到那张该死的卡。
in order to get the fucking card.
——对吗?
- That right?
不得不吻他。
Had to kiss him.
你想补偿我吗?
You wanna make it up to me?
嗯?
Huh?
-我只是，我真的很累
- I, I'm just, I'm really tired,
我只想回家
and I just, I wanna go home.
-你累了?
- Oh you're tired?
你太累了，不想舔鸡巴了，是吗?
You're too tired to suck a little dick, that it?
你是不是累得不想给我口交了?
Are you too tired to suck my dick?
-我只想回家。
- Just wanna go home.
——嘿!-我只想回家。
- Hey! - I just wanna go home.
-你太累了，不想舔我的鸡巴?
- You're too tired to suck my dick?
他妈的在这里!
Fuck over here!
(佩内洛普·尖叫)
(Penelope screams)
——不,不!
- No, no!
(脑袋嘎吱作响)(男人大叫)
(head crunching) (man yelps)
不,停止!
No, stop!
——[人]他妈的!
- [Man] Fuck!
——佩内洛普?
- Penelope?
(人们在打架)(紧张的音乐)
(people fighting) (tense music)
-[人]你!(手拍打)
- [Man] You! (hand slapping)
-[佩内洛普]住手，你弄疼我了!
- [Penelope] Stop it, you're hurting me!
你在伤害我!
You're hurting me!
放开!(紧张的音乐)
Let go! (tense music)
住手，你弄疼我了!
Stop, you're hurting me!
的帮助。
Help.
停!
Stop!
(弗兰克喘气)
(Frank panting)
-得了吧，弗兰克
- Oh, come on, Frank.
来吧,弗兰克。
Come on, Frank.
-[男人]你以为你在和谁说话?
- [Man] Think you are talking to?
(弗兰克大叫)
(Frank yells)
-你在干什么?
- What are you doing?
让她走吧!
Let her go!
(强烈的音乐)
(intense music)
(弗兰克喘气)
(Frank panting)
佩内洛普,你明白吗?
Penelope, you okay?
-我没事，我没事
- I'm okay, I'm okay.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
-你不知道你做了什么，你这个小混蛋。
- You have no idea what you've done, you little punk.
我他妈的要把你埋了。
I will fucking bury you.
——在哪里? !
- Where?!
草泥马,在哪里?
Where, motherfucker, where?
因为她会想送花的!
'Cause she's gonna want to send flowers!
-哇，哇，哇，哇，哇!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
慢点，小猫咪。
Slow down there, pussy boy.
她什么都不会给你的。
She ain't gonna send you shit.
我想你我都知道，
I think you and I both know,
你不会因此被解雇的。
you ain't got the sack for this.
(枪射击)
(gunshot firing)
(佩内洛普尖叫)(男人咕哝着)
(Penelope screams) (man grunts)
-告诉她结束了!
- Tell her it's over!
告诉她你想分手!
Tell her you want to break up!
(枪击发)
(gun cocking)
——好吧,好吧!
- Fine, fine!
我想分手，该死的，妈的!
I wanna break up, God damn it, fuck!
明白吗?
Okay?
佩内洛普，你接受他辞去你男友的职位吗?
- Penelope, do you accept his resignation as your boyfriend?
-你说的没错。
- You're God damn right I do.
——他妈的?
- The fuck?
-我恨你，你这个傻逼。
- I hate you, you dumb fucking cunt.
去你妈的。
Fuck you.
保险，因为我知道我拿着这个
Insurance, 'cause I know that me holding this
比他拿着那个更让你害怕。
scares you more than him holding that.
——跑出门去，“内洛普!”
- Run out the door, 'Nelope!
-你个混蛋。
- You fucking cunt.
去你妈的。(吐)
- Fuck you. (spits)
(希望音乐)
(hopeful music)
(轮胎尖叫)
(tires screeching)
(人的)
(man grunting)
- 827 kcwd。
- 827KCWD.
827 kcwd。
827KCWD.
-我不知道刚才发生了什么
- I don't know what happened back there,
但我真的真的很抱歉
but I'm really, really sorry.
-那是愤怒。
- That was rage.
那是纯粹的愤怒，
That was pure rage,
我不希望你为此感到抱歉
and I don't ever want you to be sorry about that.
因为如果一个男人不勃然大怒的话
'Cause if a man don't fly into a rage, then,
那他就没有恋爱。
then he isn't in love.
-“我开枪打了一个人。”
- "I shot a man."
"天啊，这姑娘就是毒品，好毒品"
"My God, this girl is drugs, good drugs."
- [Frank画外音]以及和她在一起的全部经历
- [Frank Voiceover] And the sum total experience with her
简直就是《管制药物法案》
is nothing short of the Controlled Substances Act.
但那人活该
But that man deserved it,
我开枪打了他
and I shot him.
-嗨。
- Hey.
如果我告诉你
What if I told you that,
我不想再当猎枪了?
I don't wanna be no shotgun no more?
-你他妈在说什么，内洛普?
- The fuck you talking about, 'Nelope?
-也许我想要升级，宝贝
- Well maybe I want an upgrade, baby.
不骑就死。
To ride or die.
-该死的，女孩，这完全没有道理，
- God damn it, girl, that makes no fucking sense at all,
但我喜欢它!
but I love it!
完成了!
Done!
-那我们还应该做什么疯狂的事?
- So what other crazy thing should we do?
像鞭策时刻。
Spur the moment like.
(轮胎尖叫)
(tires screeching)
-就算换了普锐斯
- Even with the Prius trade in,
那我们就快破产了。
that'll leave us almost broke.
-我不在乎你得到了什么，弗兰克
- Well, I don't care about what you got, Frank.
我只关心你能得到什么。
I only care about what you're capable of getting.
我相信你。
I believe in you.
♪我不需要很多钱♪
♪ I don't need a whole lots of money ♪
♪我不需要♪
♪ I don't need ♪
(发动机转动)(轮胎鸣叫)
(engine revving) (tires squealing)
♪一个人可以想♪
♪ A man could want ♪
♬我得到的比我想要的多
♪ I got more than I could ask for ♪
♬我也不用绕着♬跑
♪ And I don't have to run around ♪
♬我不用整晚都待在外面
♪ I don't have to stay out all night ♪
——吸引!
- Woo!
♬因为我给自己买了块糖果
♪ 'Cause I got me a sweet ♪
-怎么了，弗兰克?
- What's wrong, Frank?
-我现在感觉自己还活着。
- I just feel so fucking alive right now.
我只是，只是，
I just, I just, I,
我只是要。
I just gotta.
——要什么?
- Gotta what?
-哦，我实在受不了了。
- Oh, I just can't stand it.
我只是需要…
I just need to...
对不起，宝贝，对不起。——什么?
I'm sorry, baby, I'm sorry. - What?
(轮胎尖叫)
(tires screeching)
♬你不知道她是♬吗
♪ Don't you know that she's ♪
♬她是那么的美好
♪ She's some kind of wonderful ♪
对，她是，她是
♪ Yes, she is, she is ♪
♬她是那么的美好
♪ She's some kind of wonderful ♪
♬对，对，对，对
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪当我抱着她的时候♪
♪ When I hold her in my arms ♪
(活泼的音乐)
(lively music)
-你在干什么，宝贝?
- What are you doing, baby?
-我不想坐这些位子…
- I don't wanna get these seats...
(呻吟)
(couple moaning)
-去他的座位，弗兰克
- Fuck the seats, Frank.
♪女人，把我抱在怀里吧
♪ Woman, take me in your arms ♪
♪摇你的宝宝♪
♪ Rock your baby ♪
♪女人，把我抱在怀里吧
♪ Woman, take me in your arms ♪
♪摇你的宝宝♪
♪ Rock your baby ♪
♬什么也没有♬
♪ There's nothin' to it ♪
♬说你想怎么做就怎么做
♪ Just say you wanna do it ♪
♬打开你的心扉♬
♪ Open up your heart ♪
♪让爱开始♪
♪ And let the lovin' start ♪
-“她就是那次叛变。”
- "She was that mutiny"
“只有一定程度的欲望才能产生敬畏。”
"that only a certain level of lust can have on reverence."
毫米。
Mm.
“我希望他们每天都战斗到死。”
"And I hope they fight to the death, daily."
毫米。(笑)
Mm. (chuckles)
哦,孩子。
Oh child.
我总是害怕读下一部分，
I'm always scared to read this next part,
但我要继续读下去。
but I'm gonna keep on reading.
♪我猜你现在就要走了♪
♪ Guess that you'll be leaving now ♪
♪即使在你最深的怀疑里♪
♪ Even in your deepest doubt ♪
♪你都有了吗♪
♪ Have you got it all ♪
♬弄明白了♬
♪ Figured out ♪
-嗨。
- Hey.
嘿,弗兰克。
Hey Frank.
弗兰克。
Frank.
婴儿。
Baby.
我能告诉你一件事吗?
Can I tell you something?
-我能先告诉你一件事吗?
- Can I tell you something first?
-嗯，是的，只是
- Um, yeah, it's just that-
——这是很重要的。
- It's important.
——好的。
- Okay.
-你想要永久的抛弃。
- You wanting the throw away to be permanent.
-嗯嗯。
- Mm-hm.
-我不确定
- I wasn't sure,
但我现在是了。
but I am now.
我想让你知道
I wanted you to know,
我要把它丢在某个肮脏的卡车停车场
I'm gonna leave it in some dirty truck stop
撕了。-弗兰克
tore out somewhere. - Frank-
弗兰克，你是谁?
Frank, what are you?
弗兰克。
Frank.
该死的，弗兰克。
God damn it, Frank.
你应该让我先说。(哭)
You should have let me go first. (crying)
-宝贝，怎么了?
- Baby, what's going on?
-我本来要离开你的，弗兰克
- I was gonna leave you, Frank.
在俱乐部，弗兰克。
At the club, Frank.
天啊，我都做过几百次了。
God, I've done it hundreds of times.
我查了一下信用卡
I run the credit card
然后在你被赶出去之前我就走了，但是
and then I'm gone before you even get kicked out, but,
我不知道他会把我拽来拽去，
I didn't know that he was gonna yank me around and, and,
该死，你不该闯进来的，弗兰克。
God damn it, you weren't supposed to burst in, Frank.
从来没有人闯进来
Nobody ever fucking bursts in,
从来没有人闯进来!
nobody ever fucking bursts in!
,但是……
- But...
-我能搞定他的，弗兰克
- I coulda handled him, Frank.
我可以搞定他的。
I coulda handled him.
你不用这么做的。
You didn't have to do that.
没关系，你可以，呃，
It's fine, you can just, um,
让我在公交车站什么的下车。
drop me off at a bus stop or something.
我可以……
I can...
-但是你，你说你想和我一起去。
- But you, you told me you wanted to come with me.
-那只是说说而已，弗兰克
- Those are just words, Frank.
每个人都这么说，但没人真的这么想。
Everybody says them and nobody means them.
别，求你别那样看着我。
Don't, please don't look at me like that.
(平静的音乐)
(calming music)
♬我12岁的时候就在跳舞
♪ I was dancing when I was 12 ♪
-嗨。
- Hey.
♬我12岁的时候就在跳舞
♪ I was dancing when I was 12 ♪
这可能是个谎言。
It could all be a lie.
没关系。
It's okay.
俱乐部里的每句话。
Every word in that club.
我也不在乎
I don't care.
但刚才这是真的吗?
But was this real, just now?
因为我必须知道。
'Cause I gotta know.
-我对天发誓，是真的，弗兰克
- I swear to God, it was, Frank.
从来没有人帮过我。
I ain't never had anyone do this for me before.
我这辈子从未有过这种感觉。
I never felt this way in my life.
-那骑马和死亡的部分呢?
- And that part about ridin', and dyin'?
-是的。
- Yeah.
-那我们就粘在一起了，宝贝
- Then we're stuck together, baby.
热口香糖在停机坪上卡住了。
Hot gum on tarmac stuck.
永远不会分开。
Ain't never coming apart.
——哦,弗兰克。
- Oh Frank.
♬我八岁的时候就在跳舞
♪ I was dancing when I was eight ♪
♬跳舞是不是很奇怪
♪ Is it strange to dance ♪
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
(莫莉喘息声)
(Molly gasps)
(引擎隆隆)
(engine rumbling)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(敲窗)
(knocking on window)
——女士。
- Ma'am.
我，我知道你害怕。
I, I know you scared.
地狱，我也会是地狱。
Hell, hell I would be, too.
但是，但是，如果你打开了后备箱，
You know, but, but, but ifin you popped the trunk,
我可以换轮胎，而你，
I, I could change that tire and you,
你可以坐在那里，很安全很安全。
you could stay seated up in there nice and, nice and safe.
-我检查了后备箱，没有备用的。
- I, I checked the trunk and there's no spare.
我真的很怕你。
And I'm just really scared of you.
嗯嗯,
- Well uh,
上帝保佑。
God bless.
——对不起。
- Sorry.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
-你说得对。
- Yeah, you right.
没有备用。
There's no spare.
我可以把你拖到四英里高的水银上。
I could uh, tow you into Quicksilver, about four miles up.
我们或许可以让你重新开始
We, we could probably get you rolling again
在明天下午。
by tomorrow afternoon.
-是的。
- Yeah.
——好的。
- Okay.
好吧。
All right.
你得坐到驾驶座那边去。
You gotta get in the driver's side.
好吧，慢慢来。
Well, slide on in.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(电话拨号)
(phone dialing)
-是的。
- Yeah.
是的，我收到了一个。
Yeah I got one coming in.
-你觉得我能用上吗?
- Um, do you think maybe that I can use it?
——哦,对不起。
- Oh, sorry.
业务只使用。
Business use only.
你知道那卷起来的玻璃保护不了你，
You know that, that rolled up glass wouldn't protect you,
如果，如果真的有人想要你。
if, if someone really wanted some of you.
我，我能想到很多浪漫的事情，
And, and I, I can think of plenty of romantic things that,
有些人想对你做的事。
that some fellows would want to do to you.
该死，就这样一次又一次。
Hell, just over and over again.
而你，你大老远跑到这里，一个人。
And you, and you all the way out here, alone.
但是，但是他们是罪人，我，我知道。
But, but they sinners, and I, I know that.
你知道吗?
You know?
还有，还有，还有，为了逃避罪恶
And, and, and, and running away from sin
让我专注于，那个漏气的轮胎。
is what keep me focused solely on, on that flat tire.
我的意思是,
I mean,
除非你想要。
unless you wanted it.
因为奇索斯说
'Cause Chisos says that,
只要你有一点欲望，一切就都不一样了。
that, that little want makes all the difference.
他说，他想要，
He says that that, that want,
是什么带来了，肉体，
is what bring the carn, the carnal,
进了大教堂，进了圣洞。
into the cathedral and the, the hole into the holy.
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
(无线静态嗡嗡声)
(radio static buzzing)
我，我只是，我只是说说而已。
I, I was just, I was just talking is all.
我，我，我没别的意思。
I, I, I don't mean nothing by it.
(警报)
(sirens blaring)
-宝贝，宝贝。
- Baby, baby, baby.
——嗯,什么?
- Hm, what?
——操。
- Fuck.
他妈的,好吧。
Fuck, okay.
好了，把钱收起来，收起来。
Okay, put the money away, put the money away.
枪在哪里，枪在哪里?
Where's the gun, where's the gun?
快点。——没关系。
Hurry up. - It's okay.
-快点，快点，快点。
- Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
-[佩内洛普]没事的。
- [Penelope] It's gonna be okay.
我会跟他谈谈的，宝贝。
I, I'll just talk to him, baby.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
——美丽。
- Beautiful.
替我向罪恶问好。
Say hello to sin for me.
我喜欢每年的这个时候。
I love this time of the year.
在柏油路上到处都是经典，都要去表演。
Classics all over the blacktop, all going at the show.
你们是展示还是销售?
Y'all showing or selling?
——两个。
- Both.
谁知道呢，也许回来的时候你会让我们靠边停车，
Who knows, you might even pull us over on the way back,
开着比这更爽的车
driving in something even sweeter than this
如果我看到什么东西让我的大腿抽搐
if I see something that makes my thighs twitch.
(官笑)
(Officer chuckles)
-我不知道，亲爱的，很难打败一个68b的人，但是，
- I don't know, sweetie, it's hard to beat a 68 B, but uh,
该死，还喜欢车。
damn, likes cars, too.
你这招不错，小子。
Got yourself a good one there, son.
-拜托，他什么都没有。
- Please, he ain't got shit.
他是我哥哥。
He's my brother.
-是吗?
- Oh, is that right?
-嗯嗯。
- Mm-hm.
——好。
- Well.
那下面是什么?
So what you got under there?
——内衣。
- Underwear.
只是kiddin”。
Just kiddin'.
这是V8引擎，而且他妈的很大。
It's a V8, fuckin' big one, too.
-我打赌是的。
- I'll bet it is.
那又怎样，你要保密吗?
So what, you gonna keep it a secret?
-你知道他们怎么说吗
- Well, you know what they say,
这是一个永远不会说出口的秘密
it's the secret that's never told
这提供了最非凡的悬念。
that offers the most extraordinary suspense.
-是啊，这个不错。
- Yeah, that's a good one.
谁说的?
Who said that?
-告诉他这是唐·大蒜老爸送的
- Tell him it's from Big Daddy Don Garlic.
-大佬丹·大蒜。
- Fucking Big Daddy Dan Garlic.
- - - - - -唐。
- Don.
-我就是这个意思
- That's what I meant.
Garlets。- - - - - -唐。
- It's Garlets. - Don.
-我相信他最后一次是-
- And I believe his last was-
——Garlets。
- Garlets.
-哦，是啊，他是个很棒的踏板车司机，不是吗?
- Oh yeah, he was a hell of mopar driver, wasn't he?
-当然了
- Sure as hell was.
我喜欢他开拖把的样子。
Hell, I love the way he drove them mopers.
是他开的，没错。
He fuckin' owns 'em, he does.
-嘿，亲爱的，
- Hey, look honey,
你回来的路上有什么想炫耀的吗，
you got anything you wanna show off on the way back in,
你只要喊我一声，听到了吗?
you just gimme a holler, hear?
-你最好留心听，好兄弟。
- Well you better keep your ears on, good buddy.
-(清了清嗓子)好吧，不管怎样，
- (clears throat) Well, anyway,
我让你们靠边停车的真正原因
the real reason I pulled y'all over
你要去30英里的地方吗
is you're about to hit a stretch of about 30 miles
没有手机信号塔，
with no cell phone towers,
之后还有40英里没油了。
and no gas for another 40 miles after that.
你最好盯紧那个标尺。
You may wanna keep a close eye on that gauge.
我是说，在水银街12英里处就能买到汽油，
I mean, you can get gas in Quicksilver about 12 miles in,
但快进去，快离开那里。
but get in and get outta there.
水银掉进了矿井的水里
Mercury got in the water from that mine
把阿巴拉契亚移植手术留给他们，真是疯了。
and left them Appalachian transplants bat shit crazy.
他们还剩下什么。
What's left 'em, anyway.
我不想耽误你们的时间。
Well, I don't wanna keep y'all.
你让她开过那玩意吗?
Hey, you ever let her drive that thing?
-偶尔会。
- Every once in a while.
-因为我喜欢看美女
- 'Cause I would love to see a beauty
在美丽的车轮后面。
behind the wheel of the beauty.
(枪击发)
(gun cocking)
那是什么?
What was that?
——板球。
- Cricket.
该死的东西被困在这里了
Damn things been caught in here
因为我们在马拉松加油了。
since we got gas in Marathon.
是的，我只让他在我需要午睡的时候开车。
And yeah, I only let him drive when I need to take a nap.
让我们开关,汤米。
Let's switch, Tommy.
-如果你们想在离开这里的路上把他们抽了
- If y'all wanna smoke 'em up on the way outta here,
不是没人看。
ain't nobody looking.
你不会从我这里看到任何浆果和樱桃。
You won't see no berries and cherries from me.
-好吧，我让你坐在前排，伙计。
- Well, I'm a give you a front row seat, law man.
(欢快的音乐)(发动机转动)
(lively music) (engine revving)
(轮胎啸声)
(tires squealing)
(玛格达呜咽)
(Magda whimpering)
-就这样了
- Well, this is it.
它,它的谦逊。
It, it's humble.
但是房间很干净。
But rooms are clean though.
我，我确定。
I, I make sure.
办公室就在右边。
The, the office is there on the right.
(玛格达呜咽)
(Magda whimpering)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(电话拨号)
(phone dialing)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
-嗨，爸爸，我是莫莉。
- Hi daddy, it's Molly.
我是从汽车旅馆打来的，因为
Um, I'm calling from a motel phone 'cause,
因为我在16号公路的死角上。
'cause I'm on that dead spot on the 16.
我知道，我很抱歉，但是，听着。
And I know, I'm sorry, but, but listen.
(聊天)
(people chattering)
-[女人]我喜欢你。
- [Woman] Women I would like you.
可惜我喜欢男人。
Too bad I like guys.
喜欢你。(咯咯笑)
Like you. (giggling)
——好的。
- All right.
了解更多我不喜欢的你。
Find out a lot more about you than I like.
-我告诉过你…
- I told you...
-总之，我希望你能尽快收到这封信
- Anyway, I hope you get this soon
所以你可以来接我。
so you can come and get me.
是的。
Yeah.
好吧。
Okay.
希望明早能见到你。
Hopefully I see you in the morning.
我爱你，爸爸。(紧张的音乐)
I love you, daddy. (tense music)
-我不记得你要求使用任何额外服务。
- Didn't recall you asking to use any extra services.
-哦，我很抱歉。
- Oh, I'm, I'm sorry.
我只是打了个电话。
I just had to make a quick call.
不过你可以加到我的账单上。
Um, you can add it to my bill though.
-这取决于我，我不会收你钱的。
- It was up to me, I, I wouldn't charge you at all.
嗯，我最喜欢5个。
Well, five's my favorite.
只是它总是闻起来很香。
Just always it's always smells good.
不知道为什么。
Don't know why.
-需要证人，克利夫
- Need a witness, Cleve.
哦，哦，对不起。
Oh, oh I'm sorry.
我不知道你有客人。
I didn't realize you had company.
-哦，不，不，我们，我们刚刚结束。
- Oh no, no, we, we was just finishing up.
对了，待会儿酒吧里有免费饮料。
Oh there, there's free drinks in the bar later.
——哦,谢谢。
- Oh thanks.
我，我只是太累了。
I'm, I'm just so tired though.
-没想到你没把裤子扯破。
- Surprised you didn't rip your britches.
(忧郁的音乐)
(melancholy music)
-闭上你的臭嘴
- Shut your damn mouth.
(引擎的转速)
(engine revving)
♬奇异的优雅♬
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♬这声音多么甜美
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
♬这救了我这样的可怜虫
♪ That saved a wretch like me ♪
♪我曾经迷失♪
♪ I once was lost ♪
但现在我被找到了
♪ But now I'm found ♪
——孩子。
- Baby.
宝贝,宝贝。
Baby, baby.
宝贝,醒醒
Baby, wake up
♬曾经是盲目的，但现在我看到了♬
♪ Was blind but now I see ♪
宝贝，宝贝，醒醒。
Baby, baby, wake up.
我想我们在阿巴拉契亚怪人。
I think we got us in Appalachian weirdo.
婴儿。
Baby.
-你们好啊，你们俩。
- Well hello, you two.
抱歉，但我总是把手放在一起
Pardon, but I always put my hands together
在需要的时候，又低下了头。
in the time of need, and low and behold.
似乎我们喜欢同样的年份
Seems we like the same vintage,
只是来自不同的分支。
just from a different branch.
停了，不知道为什么。
Stopped, don't know why.
你也能载我一程吗?
Think you too could give me a ride?
——是的。——没有。
- Yes. - No.
帮不了你。
Can't help you.
但这是我的一个朋友。
But this is a friend of mine.
如果你给他打个电话，他肯定可以的。
And if you give him a call, I'm sure he can.
-我会弥补的。
- I'll make due.
——随便你。
- Suit yourself.
(光滑的音乐)
(smooth music)
(铃铛叮当声)
(bells jingling)
-抱歉我得出去，奥菲莉亚。
- Sorry I had to step out, Ophelia.
我们的水龙头漏水。
We have a leaky faucet.
我不得不去维护它。
I had to put maintenance on it.
你刚才说
So you were saying that uh,
你离开了你的丈夫
you left your husband
你是在会议上认识他的吗?
when you met this fella at a conference?
——我所做的。
- I did.
不到一个小时，我就和他在一辆车里，
Within the hour, I was in a car with him and,
我们要离开这里
and we were leaving everything
我忘记了对我很重要
that I forgot was important to me.
我离开时大卫六岁。
David was six when I left.
还有，小劳里才三岁。
And, (cries) little Laurie was three.
我已经37年没见过我的孩子，也没和他们说过话了。
I haven't seen or spoke to my babies in 37 years.
37年。
37 years.
-你活该吗?
- Does it serve you right?
-我想是的。——嗯。
- I suppose it does. - Hm.
我在登记簿上看到你叫奥菲莉亚·温德尔。
I saw you listed on the register as an Ophelia Wendall.
那是你的还是他的?
Is that your maiden or his?
-不，我从没想过要改姓。
- Oh no, I never wanted to change my last name.
-你知道，这看起来不太对
- You know, it don't really seem right
和孩子们共享名字
sharing names with little ones
当你只捐出自然
when you only donated the nature
逃离了养育。
and ran away from the nurture.
希望你的心与主同在。
Hope you got your heart right with the Lord.
-我想我现在要结账了。
- I think I'll take my check now.
-不，不，真相没有支票。
- No, no, there's no check for the truth.
你讲得光明正大。
You told it fair and square.
-祝你今天愉快。
- Have a nice day.
-就这么定了。
- Well it's settled.
你不能容忍通奸。
You don't hold no truck with adultery.
什么?
What?
——什么都没有。
- Nothing.
你盯上了奇索斯。
You got Chisos pegged.
如果他在这里，我
Hell, if he was here, I,
我猜想闪电从天堂降临
I reckon lightning come down from heaven,
把那个奸夫当场打死。
strike that adulterer dead on the spot.
-你很清楚上帝不会这么做的。
- You know damn well the Lord don't work like that.
我们要做他的遗嘱。
We gotta do his will.
-我现在就去告诉琦琦。
- Well, I'll go tell Cookie now.
-是的。
- Yeah.
(引擎隆隆)
(engine rumbling)
♪旋律的日子里我都做了什么♪
♪ Melody day what have I done ♪
现在我们的心又被紧紧地锁住了
♪ Now our hearts are locked up tight again ♪
当我祈祷这一切都开始的时候
♪ And when I pray it's all begun ♪
♪当你微笑的时候它又融化了♪
♪ And when you smile it melts away again ♪
(玛格达呜咽)
(Magda whimpering)
-就这么说吧，这就是原因。
- So say so, that's why.
♪就在那里♪
♪ Be there ♪
车，车，车，有人来了。
Car, car, car, somebody coming.
某人,某人,某人。
Somebody, somebody, somebody.
的借口。
Excuse there.
我能帮你吗?
Can, can I help you?
-我在找房间。
- Just looking for a room.
-如果有蜜月套房的话。
- Honeymoon suite if you got one.
-是的，如果你有的话，加满油。
- Yeah, if you got it, and a fill up.
-你，你，你们俩不是在吸大麻吧?
- You, you, you two ain't on the marijuana, are ya?
因为，呃，因为我们这里没有瘾君子。
'Cause uh, 'cause we don't keep with no drug addicts here.
——没有。
- No.
不，先生，以上都不是。
No sir, none of the above.
-不，绝对不是瘾君子。
- Nope, definitely not drug dicks.
-是的。
- Yeah.
好吧。
Okay then.
呃，呃，库克，
Well uh, uh Cook,
小甜饼可以帮你填，
Cookie here can uh help you out with the fill,
我们看看能不能给你找个干净的房间
and uh, we'll see if we can find you a clean room
适合一个新的联盟。
fitting for a, a new union.
好了，你们能在这里签个名吗。
All right, if uh, y'all could just sign in here.
现在我们有一个国王，后面床头有花。
Now we have a, a king with a flower back headboard.
每个人40美元。
That's uh, uh 40 per.
,好吗?
That okay?
-嗯嗯。
- Mm-hm.
-哦，不，不。
- Oh no, no.
我们，我们明早再算账，
We, we'll settle up in the morning,
如果，如果你们要吃饭的话。
if, if y'all gonna eat.
-该死，她真漂亮。
- Damn, she's beautiful.
——那是什么?
- What's that?
哦，是的，他们都是。
Oh uh, yeah, they all are.
谁把她吊死的?
- Who'd a hung her?
-她被咬了，不是吗?
- She took the bite, didn't she?
-我们会把花拿回去的，拜托了
- We'll take the flower back, please.
-现在，呃，天黑后酒吧里有饮料。
- Now there's uh, there's drinks in the bar after dark.
如果你们和梅布尔坐在一起，就把这个给她。
If y'all sit with Mabel, just, just give her this.
——梅布尔是谁?
- Who's Mabel?
-美宝莲，她是我的，她是我的妻子。
- Oh, Maybelline, she, she's my, she's my wife.
她，她经营酒吧和餐厅。
She, she runs the, the bar and the, the diner.
这里有点寂寞，所以，
It gets kind of lonely out here, so uh,
所以如果你们有故事要讲，
so ifin y'all got a story to tell,
她会很乐意听的。
she'll be happy to listen.
前两个是免费的。
First two are free.
合计是什么意思?
What's TOT mean?
-真理表。
- Table of truth.
如果你在说谎，她会知道的。
And uh, she'll know if you're lying.
-我们不能错过这样的机会，
- We can't miss out on an opportunity like that,
现在可以了吗，宝贝?
now can we, baby?
-他们把车开走了吗?
- Did they move the car?
-就在房间前面。
- It's right in front of the room.
(强烈的音乐)
(intense music)
-我给你准备好了
- I got it all topped off and ready for you.
停在你房间前面。
Parked it in front of your room.
甚至为你洗了挡风玻璃。
Even washed the windshield for you.
-嘿，你不介意我梳洗一下然后在酒吧见你吧?
- Hey, you mind if I freshen up and meet you at the bar?
——好的。
- Okay.
嘿。
Hey.
——(佩内洛普·)是吗?
- [Penelope] Yeah?
-你走开的时候我能打你屁股吗?
- Can I swat you on the ass as you walk away?
我，我一直想这么做。
I, I always wanted to do that.
-你不用问的，宝贝。
- You don't have to ask, baby.
只是摇摆。
Just swing it.
(可爱的音乐)
(endearing music)
(可怕的音乐)
(eerie music)
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
(饼干的)
(Cookie grunting)
-我很抱歉
- I'm sorry about this,
但你不该那么做的。
But you shouldn't have done what you done.
别担心，我们会治好你的。
Don't worry, we'll fix ya.
等我把这个修好。
Right after I fix this one.
(肉压制)
(flesh squelching)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
(莫莉喘息声)
(Molly gasps)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
我想那个女孩听到了。
I think that girl heard me.
然后，然后她，她就盯着我看。
And, and then she was, she was staring right at me.
-她会听到什么，琦琦?
- And what would she have heard, Cookie?
一个满脸皱纹的老太太被人用脚吊起来的声音?
The sound of a wrinkly old lady being strung up by her foot?
她甚至说不出那首曲子的名字。
She couldn't even name that tune with all the notes.
-你没告诉我有人在角落里。
- You didn't tell me there was somebody in the corner room.
-我今天才帮她登记入住
- Well, I just checked her in today.
-但你没告诉我。
- But you didn't tell me.
不应该有什么人。
There wasn't supposed to be nobody.
我就不会拿着那位女士的，
I wouldn't have been carrying that lady's,
我是说，如果我知道有人
I mean, if I knew that there was somebody
我就不会背着那条腿了。
I wouldn't have been carrying the leg.
-好吧，好吧，好吧
- Okay, okay, okay.
我去看看她。
I'll go check on her.
(敲的门)
(knocking on door)
——(克里夫)小姐?
- [Cleve] Miss?
你，你，你还好吗?
You, you, you okay in there?
-是的，都很好。
- Yep, all good.
-哦,好的。
- Oh, okay.
你知道，我只是，我只是，
Well, you know, I was, I was just uh,
我只是来看看你，因为
I was just checking on you 'cause um,
因为，因为你不吃晚饭
'cause, 'cause you ain't take no dinner and,
见鬼，你整晚都没探出头来。
and hell you, you ain't poked your head out all night.
我只是想看看你怎么样了。
So uh, so I was just checking on you.
确保你没事。
Make sure you, you's okay.
-我很好。
- I'm okay.
我只是，我只是偏头痛。
I just, I just get migraines.
-我可以给你带点东西，如果，如果
- Oh, I could bring you something if, if,
如果那样会有帮助。
ifin that would help.
-不，没关系。
- Nope, that's okay.
-当然，当然。
- Oh, sure, sure.
我只是，我只是，我只是想说，
Well, I just, I just um, I, I just wanna say um,
之前的事我很抱歉。
I'm, I'm sorry about before.
当我，当我，
When I, when I,
当我碰。-没关系。
when I touched- - That's okay.
——好的。
- Okay.
那好吧。
All right then, uh.
晚安。
Goodnight.
——晚安。
- Goodnight.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(可怕的音乐)
(eerie music)
-奇索斯说，大多数人会接受双重谎言
- Chisos says most people take double helpings of a lie
如果味道好。
if it tastes good.
给狗狗们留下一盘健康的真相。
Leave a healthy plate of truth out for the dogs.
——不是我。
- Not me.
-是的，我想这取决于你对谁有罪。
- Yeah, I guess it depends on who you're sinning against.
-智索的话语不会说谎，孩子。
- Chisos words don't lie, child.
-等等，谁是芝士酱?
- Wait a minute, who's Cheese Sauce?
Chisos。
- It's Chisos.
没有什么比不从他嘴里说出来更强大的了。
Ain't nothing more powerful than won't come outta his mouth.
我看到了他的话
And I seen his words
让一列尖叫的货运列车完全停下来。
bring a screaming freight train to a complete stop.
-你是说真的火车吗?
- You mean like an actual train?
-像小火车?
- Like a choo choo?
-是的，亲爱的，一辆真正的火车。
- Yes, darling, an actual choo choo.
他是从楼上餐厅的前窗下手的。
He done it from the front window in the diner upstairs.
一群怀疑者听到了Butte的Stud线的到来。
A bunch of doubters heard the Stud of Butte line coming.
他站起来，像这样伸出双手，
He rose up and held out his hands like this,
说了几句盖尔语。
said a few of those Gaelic words.
几英里外就能听到刹车声。
You could hear those brakes from miles away.
36辆车全部停了下来。
All 36 cars come to a complete stop.
再多说几句，他就把话说回来了。
Few more words, he even made it back up.
-你确定不是偏离轨道了?
- You sure it wasn't just side tracked?
(铃铛叮当声)
(bells jingling)
-那是侧道。
- It was side tracking.
你们俩肯定见过车是怎么被撞的。
I'm sure you two have seen it done to a car.
我说的对吗?
Am I right?
-我看你把它开起来了，是吧?
- I see you got it running, huh?
-只是保险丝。
- It's just a fuse.
我只是用中指挠了一下痒
Just a little tickle with my middle finger
它马上就火了。
and it fired right up.
-天啊，宝贝，你听到了吗?
- Oh my God, baby, did you just hear that?
在远处的某个地方
Somewhere off in the distance
一辆货运火车掉头了。
a freight train just made a fucking U-turn.
(笑着说)
(people laughing)
——我Chisos。
- I'm Chisos.
-哦，我是弗兰克。
- Oh, I'm Frank.
- - -弗兰克。
- Frank.
嘿，你们俩是度蜜月的。
Hey, you two are honeymooners.
是这样吗?
Is that right?
-对，没错。
- Yeah, that's right.
我们有您的特大号
We got your king size
后面还有花床头板和其他东西。
with the flower back headboard and everything.
我们尽量不吵醒你。
We'll try not to wake you.
-你知道他们怎么说吗
- You know what they say,
你在真相出来前5天撒了谎，
you throw a lie in a river five days before the truth,
真相迟早会大白的
the truth is gonna catch up.
-尤其是在这张桌子上。
- Especially at this table.
-大多数人都是无缘无故逃出来的
- Most don't make it out here without a reason.
因为我们不走寻常路。
Being that we're off the beaten path and all.
告诉我，你们这对新婚夫妇要去哪里?
So tell me, where are you newly weds headed?
-你看，作为结婚礼物
- Well, see, as a, as a wedding gift,
我的新丈夫，是的，
my new husband, yeah,
他答应要扳倒我
he's promised to take me down
这是世界上最美的路。
the prettiest road in the whole fuckin' world.
-好吧，你-
- Oh well, you-
-这个世界不该来这里
- Well this is the wrong part of the world
去寻找最美丽的道路。
to find the prettiest road.
-是啊，不是在这个臭地方
- Yeah, it ain't in this stink hole.
这是西方。
It's west.
我的宝贝，他说他在电影里看到的，
My baby here, he said that he saw it in some movie,
《末路狂花》。"
uh, "Thelma & Louise."
他们走的就是这条路
It's this road that they go down
在电影的结尾，
at the end of the movie,
还有我的宝贝，他要带我去兜风。
and my baby here, he's gonna take me for a ride.
——哇。
- Wow.
你是一个多么慷慨善良的人啊。
What a generous and kind man you are.
我看过那部电影。
I've seen that movie.
很神奇的。
Amazing.
看到一对情侣要带对方去兜风。
To see two love birds about to take each other for a ride.
我能和你们一起去吗?
You mind if I join you two?
-除非你有故事。
- Well only if you have a story.
你知道的，因为这是规则。
You know, seeing as how that's the rules and all.
-给我们两个。
- Get us two.
-就两个?
- Just, just two?
-只为我们男人。
- Just for us men.
-[梅布尔]哦。
- [Mabel] Oh.
-那么，呃，你在这里做什么?
- So uh, what is it you do out here?
-简而言之，
- But the short version though,
因为我已经准备好做床头板了。
'cause I'm about ready for that headboard.
-真相不能被删减。
- Well the truth can't be truncated.
-那就尽力吧。
- Well, try your best.
-克利夫斯怎么样?
- How's this for Cliffs?
他们一家1903年从阿巴拉契亚出来。
Family came out from Appalachia in 1903.
这个矿井是我家祖祖辈辈传下来的。
This mine's been in my family for generations.
我们曾是世界水银之都，
We were the mercury capital of the world,
直到矿井坍塌。
till the mine collapsed.
我祖父被困在矿井下。
My grandfather was trapped underneath that mine.
他领导了一个释放杀人犯的监狱工作计划，
He was leading a prison work release program for murderers,
强奸犯，各种污秽。
rapists, all kinds of filth.
他们被留在那里等死，
They were left there for dead,
直到11天后他走了出来
until he came walking out 11 days later
当板块移动时。
when the plate shifted.
他是唯一一个活下来的。
He was the only one that made it.
三个重罪犯死在下面，被咬得只剩骨头。
Three dead felons left below, gnawed to the bone.
——这是疯了。
- That's crazy.
-看我祖父他靠吃罪人活下来
- See my grandfather, he survived by eating those sinners,
器官。
organs and all.
不是一个秘密。
Not a secret.
到处都是报纸。
Made the papers everywhere.
什么是秘密，我们还在
What is a secret is that we are still
阿巴拉契亚的食罪者是我们的核心。
Appalachian sin eaters at our core.
几个世纪以来我们一直如此。
We have been for centuries.
它流淌在我们的血液里。
It's in our blood.
所以所有的流浪者，旅行者，所有的奔跑者，
So all the drifters, the travelers, all the runners,
他们来到这里，坐在这张桌子前忏悔，
they come and sit down here at this table and confess,
我们的消耗与罪的严重程度成正比。
and we consume in proportion to the severity of the sin.
有时候只是耳朵后面的BB。
Sometimes it's just a BB behind the ear.
有时是无法生存的菲力牛排
Sometimes it's an unsurvivable filet,
够六个人吃的。
enough for a table of six.
-他在干什么?
- What's he doing?
-当他不让他们离开时，他总是这样做。
- What he always does when he ain't gonna let 'em leave.
给他们灌输一个难以置信的真相。
Fills them with a truth that's too hard to believe.
-我们把手机带到华雷斯，然后扔掉
- We take the cell phones down the Juarez, we dump 'em.
我们把尸体和车都烧了。
We burn the bodies and the cars.
没人知道是我们干的
No one has any idea that it is us
这就承担了负担
that takes on the burden
否则世界将不得不承受。
that the world would otherwise have to carry.
我有同样的机会犯错，
I'm equal opportunity to at fault,
即使是我自己。
even when it comes to myself.
有时我尝到了自己罪恶的滋味。
Sometimes I consume a taste of my own sin.
——啊。——耶稣基督。
- Ugh. - Jesus Christ.
-我开玩笑的。
- I'm just kidding.
但是火车的部分，是真的。
But the train part, that's true.
在一角钱上随心所欲。
At will on a dime.
而且不是无生命的火车头。
And just not inanimate locomotives.
-比如什么?
- Like what else?
——人。
- People.
我知道所有的动机，
I know all about incentives,
动机和整体心理学。
motivations and overall psychology.
——好的。
- Okay.
试着我,弗洛伊德。
Try me, Freud.
-我的家族拥有6000多英亩的土地
- My family owned over 6,000 mercury rich acres,
但现在只剩我一个人了
but now I'm the only one left.
去年4月，我以2400万美元的价格卖掉了几乎所有的房子。
So last April, I sold almost all of it for $24 million.
现在我没人可以花钱了。
Now I have no one to spend it on.
没人给我生孩子。
No one to give me a child.
我真的想要一个，不仅仅是因为遗产的原因。
And I really want one, for more than just legacy reasons.
山顶上那间不起眼的小房子，
That modest little house up there at the top of the hill,
你可能见过。
you might have seen it.
这一切都可能是你的。
All of it could be yours.
我的诚实和忠诚几乎到了极点。
I'm honest and faithful, almost to a fault.
如果你感兴趣的话，
So if any of that interests you,
那就起身去那辆白色的车。
then get up and head out to the white car.
——“Nelope。
- 'Nelope.
-我在那儿等你。
- I'll meet you there.
(聊天)
(people chattering)
-我有话要说
- I'm gonna have a word here
确保他得到同等的报酬。
and make sure he's equally compensated.
-“内洛普，看着我。
- 'Nelope, look at me.
,“Nelope Nelope !
'Nelope, 'Nelope!
-儿子，儿子，儿子，她是脱衣舞女，她是骗子。
- Son, son, son, she's a stripper, she's a grifter.
他们都卖。
They all sell it.
如果她还没有把你当成她的一切，她会的。
If she hasn't taken you for everything, she will.
-不，她不是。
- No, she's not.
-所以我要给你一叠漂亮的现金。
- So I'm gonna get a nice little wad of cash for ya.
当你退房的时候，这将有助于治愈那颗破碎的心。
When you check out, it'll help to heal that broken heart.
-如果他今天不喝，那就是早上的咖啡。
- Morning coffee if he won't take it today.
-嘿，你不吃完吗?
- Hey, aren't you gonna finish that?
这是蒸馏地狱酒的佳酿。
It's a wonderful vintage of distilled damnation right there.
(手把)
(hand slamming)
——(佩内洛普·)嘿。
- [Penelope] Hey.
-该死的，我爱你。
- God damn I love you, 'Nelope.
-抱歉，我得去嘘嘘
- Sorry, I had to tinkle,
我再也受不了他吐出来的那些垃圾了
and I couldn't take any more of that garbage he was spewing.
你还记得那些你从没告诉过我的事吗
Hey, you know all those ways you never told me
你打算怎么上我?
how you were gonna fuck me?
好吧，你能不能忘了他们
Well, could you just forget about 'em
过来和我做爱
and come over here and make love to me
很长一段时间?
for a really long time?
-在那之后，你连说话的机会都没有。
- After that, girl, you don't even get a say.
(浪漫的音乐)
(romantic music)
♬你从摇摇欲坠的桥上跳下去
♪ You leapt from crumbling bridges ♪
♬看着城市的风景化为尘土
♪ Watching city scapes turn to dust ♪
♬拍摄直升机坠毁♬
♪ Filming helicopters crashing ♪
♪在遥远的海洋里♪
♪ In the ocean from way above ♪
♬你有音乐的天赋，宝贝告诉我为什么
♪ Got the music in you baby tell me why ♪
♬你被永远锁在这里了
♪ You've been locked in here forever ♪
♬你就是不能说再见♬
♪ And you just can't say goodbye ♪
(Chisos吸入)
(Chisos inhales)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
-拖车司机
- The tow truck driver,
他把他的手放在…
he put, he put his hand on my, on...
我很好。
I'm okay though.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
-你真的搞砸了
- You fucked up really bad,
你得把它改正过来。
and you're gonna have to make it right.
——好的。
- Okay.
-你的新生儿还没出生两个月
- You got a newborn not two months in the ground
你已经被你的淫欲牵着鼻子走了。
and you're already letting your lustful ways lead you.
——我?
- Do I?
我做了什么?
Do I?
-你在抱怨什么?
- What do you whine about?
-闭嘴，闭嘴
- Oh shut up, just shut up.
——什么?
- What?
-你告诉我梅布尔两个月前是怎么给我生的一个男孩
- You tell me how Mabel give me a, a boy two months ago,
她和我在一起三年了，没有迟到过。
and she ain't late with me in, in three years.
你告诉我怎么做?
You tell me how, huh?
让我明白,
Make me understand-
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
-她爸爸给这个号码打了19次电话
- 19 Calls from her daddy to this number
早上6:24开始。
starting at 6:24 AM.
我查了号码，他是桑都斯县警长。
I researched the number, he's a Sanctus County Sheriff.
他在南616号，琦琦说她看到他拿着
He'll be 616 South, and Cookie said she saw him holding-
——走吧。
- Go.
你也一样。
You too.
(车门关闭)
(car doors closing)
(引擎啸声)
(engine squealing)
-来吧，爸爸。
- Come on, daddy.
你在哪里?
Where are you?
-该死的，我喜欢在你身边醒来。
- God damn I love waking up next to you, 'Nelope.
-我不敢相信你以为我会离开你
- I can't believe you thought I was gonna leave you
来做芝士酱。
for the Cheese Sauce.
那个白痴根本赢不了我的弗兰克。
That idiot doesn't stand a chance against my Frank.
-我们被困在一起了，宝贝。
- [Frank] We're stuck together, baby.
-就像热口香糖粘在停机坪上。
- Like hot gum on tarmac stuck.
(古怪的音乐)
(whimsical music)
天呐
Holy shit.
这是真实的吗?
Is this real?
-这是另一个吗?
- Is that another?
-我的天啊，和兔八哥一样高的克拉数
- Oh my God, a Bugs Bunny level of karats if I ever did see.
-你愿意用这颗钻石结婚吗?
- With this diamond will thee wed?
——不!
- Don't!
别再这么做了，除非你是认真的。
And don't you never do that again, unless you mean it.
——好的。
- Okay.
我只是在开玩笑。
I was just kidding.
——我是认真的。
- I'm serious.
——好的。
- Okay.
-我不是开玩笑。
- I'm not a joke.
-我对天发誓，总有一天我会给你惊喜的。
- Swear to God I'm gonna surprise you one day, 'Nelope.
-只是说说而已。
- They's just words.
——早上。
- Morning.
只要两份早餐，谢谢。
Just uh, two for breakfast, please.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(贝尔钩缝)
(bell dinging)
-你想去哪儿都行
- Uh, yeah, anywhere you want.
-我喜欢吃蛋糕，琦琦。
- I'm a go with them cakes, Cookie.
该死，这太棒了。
Damn, this is amazing.
——嗯?
- Hm?
-我爸爸是海军陆战队员
- My dad was a Marine.
-你们俩关系好吗?
- You two close?
-是的，真的。
- Yeah, were really.
我16岁时失去了他。
Lost him when I was 16.
-哦，对不起。
- Oh, I'm sorry.
-别这样，因为我16岁就和他在一起了
- Don't be, 'cause my 16 with him
总比100个人跟任何次等男人在一起要好。
was better than 100 would've been with any lesser man.
我本来打算参军的，但我父亲死后，
I planned enlisting myself, but uh, after my dad died,
我得照顾我妈妈和妹妹。
I had to take care of my mom and little sister.
-我打赌他为你感到骄傲，弗兰克
- I bet he's proud of you, Frank.
——希望如此。
- Hope so.
——他是。
- He is.
那你呢，弗兰克?
And what about you, Frank?
你想要自己的孩子吗?
Do you want any babies of your own?
-从没不想要他们。
- Never not wanted 'em.
你吗?
You?
-我现在才知道。
- Well, I haven't until now.
带他。
Take him.
——什么?
- What?
——带他。
- Take him.
(可爱的音乐)
(endearing music)
-给我滚下车。
- Get your ass outta the car.
我怎么跟你说的?——不,拜托!
What did I tell ya? - No, please!
-搞什么，是你让我-
- What the, you're the one that made me-
(警报)
(sirens blaring)
——带他。
- Take him.
带他一起走。
Take him with you.
他会是我们的保护者。
He'll be our protector.
你的爸爸。
Your dad.
(玛格达呜咽)
(Magda whimpering)
只是带他。
Just take him.
(玛格达尖叫)(叮铃)
(Magda squealing) (bell dinging)
(汽笛鸣响)(克利夫大喊)
(sirens blaring) (Cleve yelling)
——嘿!
- Hey!
嘿，别闹了。
Hey, knock that shit off.
别碰她!
Get your hands off of her!
转过去，转过去。
Turn around, turn around.
——她是
- She was-
-转过去，把手放在引擎盖上。
- Turn around, put your hands on the hood.
你没事吧,亲爱的?
You okay, sweetie?
-是的。
- Yeah.
——是吗?-我很好。
- Yeah? - I'm okay.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
-什么样的男人会那样对女士动手动脚啊?
- What kind of man puts his hands on a lady like that, huh?
你怎么了，孩子?
What is wrong with you, boy?
(枪射击)
(gunshot firing)
(希望音乐)
(hopeful music)
(玛格达尖叫)(叮铃)
(Magda squealing) (bell dinging)
——嘿!
- Hey!
——冻结!
- Freeze!
哦,了不起!
Uh, something!
-是啊，不许动，你这该死的怪胎!
- Yeah, freeze it right, you fuckin' weirdo!
-内洛普，去开车。
- 'Nelope, go get the car.
-我这就去。
- I'm on it.
-你，放下枪!
- You, drop that shotgun!
还有你，给我闭嘴!
And you, shut the fuck up!
谢谢你！
Thank you.
(希望音乐)
(hopeful music)
-刚才发生了什么?
- What the hell just happened?
向右转。
Turn right.
右转，混蛋。
Turn right you motherfucker.
(轮胎尖叫)
(tires screeching)
(电话响了)
(phone ringing)
两个在绿色的车里。
Two in the green car.
-收到，他们过不了我们这关
- Copy that, they will not get past us.
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
说曹操，曹操到。
- Speak of the devil.
——操。
- Fuck.
他们要来个180度大转弯。
They're making a U-turn.
-快，快，快。
- Go, go, go.
-没事的，宝贝
- It's okay, baby.
可能是之前的那个人。
It's probably just that guy from before.
我想他喜欢我。
I think he likes me.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
- - - - - -那是谁?
- Who's that?
——嗯。
- Hm.
(弗兰克嘟哝)
(Frank grunting)
嘿，我的朋友呢?
Hey, where's my buddy?
(佩内洛普·喘息声)
(Penelope gasps)
弗兰克!
Frank!
(泰瑟枪的嗡嗡声)(激烈的音乐)
(taser buzzing) (intense music)
-嘿，嘿，嘿!
- Hey, hey, hey!
嘿，那个，那个女孩!
Hey, the, the girl!
-你带长条的吗?
- You bring the long?
——嗯。
- Uh.
呃。
Uh.
哦。
Oh.
(枪射击)
(gunshot firing)
去得到她。
Go get her.
♬现在这个世界需要什么呢
♪ What the world needs now ♪
♪是爱情的甜蜜♪
♪ Is love sweet love ♪
♬这是唯一的♬
♪ It's the only thing ♪
(女孩尖叫)
(girl screaming)
♪那只是太，哦♪
♪ That there's just too, oh ♪
♬现在这个世界需要什么呢
♪ What the world needs now ♪
♪是爱情的甜蜜♪
♪ Is love sweet love ♪
不，不是只为某一个♬
♪ No, not just for some ♪
♪但是对于每个人♪
♪ But for everyone ♪
♪为了每个人♪
♪ For everyone ♪
主啊，我们不需要另一座山
♪ Lord we don't need another mountain ♪
♪这里有足够多的山和山坡可以爬
♪ There are mountains and hillsides enough to climb ♪
♪有太多的海洋和河流等着你去跨越
♪ There are oceans and rivers enough to cross ♪
♪直到时间的尽头♪
♪ Till the end of time ♪
希望你的心与主同在，
Hope you got your heart right with the Lord,
你肮脏的妓女。
you filthy whore.
♪是爱情甜蜜的♪甜蜜的爱情
♪ Is love sweet sweet love ♪
♬这是我们唯一的想法
♪ It's the only thing we think ♪
♪。♪实在是太少
♪ That there's just too little of ♪
♪这个世界的♪太少了
♪ That the world's got too little of ♪
♬现在这个世界需要什么呢
♪ What the world needs now ♪
♪是爱情甜蜜的♪甜蜜的爱情
♪ Is love sweet sweet love ♪
不，不是只为某一个♬
♪ No, not just for some ♪
♪但是为了每个人，为了每个人
♪ But for everyone, for everyone ♪
这家伙要下坑了。
Fellow here goes to the pit.
现在!
Now!
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
-她怎么了?
- What about her?
-我们在清洗，但我不会碰它。
- We're cleansing, but I ain't touching it.
饼干!
Cookie!
饼干。
Cookie.
-我抬不起来。
- I can't lift 'em.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
-把这个收起来。
- Take this one and get her stowed.
他在路上，我们有负担要消耗。
He's on his way and we've got a burden to consume.
有需要就用这个。
Hey, use this if there's a need.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(饼干嗅探)
(Cookie sniffing)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(饼干轻轻咆哮)
(Cookie lightly growling)
(玛格达呜咽)
(Magda whimpering)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
-他已经上去了
- He's, he's already up there.
——好。
- Good.
(梅布尔喘息声)
(Mabel gasps)
把她弄干净，给我准备好。
Get her cleaned and ready for me.
——好的。
- Okay.
-温柔的抚摸。
- And with a gentle touch.
(梅布尔喘气)
(Mabel panting)
-把水管递给我。
- Hand me the hose.
温柔的接触。
Gentle touch.
-你不是应该用海绵擦吗?
- Ain't you supposed to sponge it?
-告诉过你，我不会碰它。
- Told you, I ain't touching it.
-你想从头到脚擦吗，去吧。
- You wanna sponge it head to toe, go ahead.
你就是不明白，
You just don't understand,
在我们这婊子的胯下没有收获。
there ain't no harvest between our whore's legs.
(佩内洛普·呜咽)
(Penelope whimpering)
-亲爱的主，我们接受这圣餐
- Dear Lord, we take this Eucharist,
你你最后的礼物，正义之人的食粮，
your your last living gift, the righteous man's sustenance,
感谢主给我们带来生育的器皿
and we thank you Lord for bringing us a fertile vessel
这样我们才能继续你的工作，
so that we may continue your work,
分辨羊群和牧羊人，
to discern the sheep from the shepherd,
只有到那时，我们才能进餐和净化
and only then will we dine and cleanse
直到羊都没了。
until the sheep are no more.
-[信徒]洗净我的罪孽，
- [Followers] Wash me thoroughly from my iniquities,
洗净我的…
and cleanse me from my...
——罪。
- Sin.
——(追随者)阿门。
- [Followers] Amen.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(弗兰克嘟哝)
(Frank grunting)
-你试的时间比他们都长。
- You tried longer than all of them.
(弗兰克喘气)
(Frank panting)
-她在哪里?
- Where is she?
-在等我。
- Waiting for me.
-不，不，她不是，她永远不会是。
- No, no she's not, and she never will be.
-我想你会大吃一惊的
- Oh, I think you'll be surprised.
-不，我不会的，这次不会
- No, I won't be, not this time.
我等了一辈子
I've waited my whole life
在过去的48小时里陪着她，
to spend the last 48 hours with her,
即使我只能得到这些
and even if that's all I ever get,
它会让你所有的感觉都相形见绌。
it'll dwarf anything you've ever felt.
她和我的爱是死亡也无法偷走的
She and I have a love not even death could steal,
你知道的。
and you know that.
你只会在书里读到过，
It's the kind you've only ever read about in books,
你永远也得不到。
and you'll never get it.
-你知道我最讨厌什么吗?
- You know what I hate more than anything?
虚伪。
Hypocrisy.
全世界都是无知的指手画脚者，
The whole world's full of uneducated finger pointers,
主要是指像我这样的人。
pointing mostly at people like me.
但毫无疑问，
But make no mistake about it,
我们从永恒的诅咒中拯救灵魂。
we save souls from eternal damnation.
这就是食罪者所做的。
That's what sin eaters do.
孩子，那是一桶60加仑的纯净水。
Son, that's a 60 gallon drum of purified water.
至少还能活几个星期。
That's survival for at least a couple weeks.
当然，除非你饿死。
Unless, of course, you starve.
告诉我，小子，
So tell me, punk,
还有多久你就会咬一口，成为我们的一员。
how long until you take a bite and become one of us.
-如果你敢碰她，我发誓
- If you touch her, I swear to God,
无论如何，总有一天，我会找到你。
somehow, someday, I will find you.
-这又不是蝙蝠侠
- This isn't a Batman episode.
你休想离开这里。
You're not getting outta here.
——“Nelope !
- 'Nelope!
“Nelope !
'Nelope!
我来了!
I'm coming!
-他在哪里?
- Where is he?
他死了吗?
Is he dead?
-有一点是肯定的，他不会来找你的。
- One thing's for sure, he's, he's not coming for ya.
-你不了解弗兰克
- You don't know Frank.
-我想我知道
- Oh, I think I do.
-你想要什么?
- What do you want?
-你这辈子都在放弃什么。
- What you've been giving away your entire life.
我突然想要，你却把它从架子上拿了下来?
All of a sudden I want it and you take it off the shelf?
这是为什么呢?
Why is that?
-我是非卖品
- I ain't for sale.
我从来没去过。
I never have been.
-我打赌外面有很多充气的鸡巴
- I bet there's a lot of inflated dicks out there
这将不同意。
that would disagree.
一个是什么?
What's one more?
——去你妈的!
- Fuck you!
-你昨晚就该去散步。
- You should have taken that walk last night.
我知道你考虑过，但你知道，
I know you thought about it, but you know,
你去找他，这让我很伤心。
you went to him and that just breaks my heart.
-你没有心碎。
- You don't have a heart to break.
-你要给我一个孩子。
- You're going to give me a child.
这是一个事实。
That's a fact.
我宁愿用宠溺而不是用爪子。
I'd rather do it with a coddle then a claw.
我的意思是,
I mean originally,
自然界的每一个生育行为都是一场强奸。
every single act procreation in nature was a rape.
只有人类问道。
Only humans asked.
-你别碰我。
- You ain't touching me.
-为什么突然这么值钱了。
- Why is it so valuable all of a sudden.
我是说，你一直在使用上帝的生殖系统
I mean, you've been using God's reproductive system
作为你一生的工具。
as a tool your entire life.
我是说，要么性爱是无意义的，要么强奸是不好的。
I mean, either sex is meaningless or rape is bad.
不能两者兼而有之。
Can't be both.
-是握着礼物的手
- It's the hand that holds the gift
可以改变盒子里的东西，
that can change what's in the box,
我从来都不愿意让别人免费给我。
and I ain't ever willingly held it out for free.
一次也没有。
Not once.
不是没有人。
Not for nobody.
除了弗兰克。
Except Frank.
你以为你已经谈完了
You think you's talking over
一个卑微的脱衣舞女的脑袋，对吧?
a lowly stripper's head all the time, don't ya?
会把你生吞活剥
Just eats you alive
我有一列满载爱的火车只为他而开
that I got a freight train of love headed only for him,
即使是你也无法改变它。
and not even you can budge it.
-我可以爱你
- I could love you,
如果你愿意的话。
if you let me.
想想。
Think about it.
明天早上见。
I'll see you in the morning.
——没有。
- No.
在我心里，我知道他是来找我的。
Somehow in my heart I know he's coming for me.
-[电台传道者]谁会感到羞愧。
- [Radio Preacher] Who will be put to shame.
(用外语)
(speaking in foreign language)
在希腊,
In Greek,
你会因为这种错误的自信而感到羞辱。
you will be humiliated by this misplaced confidence.
(无线聊天)
(Radio chattering)
所以他在诗篇第5章说…
So he says in Psalms 5...
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
——爸爸。
- Daddy.
爸爸,爸爸。
Dad, daddy.
(莫莉尖叫)
(Molly screaming)
不!
No!
爸爸。
Daddy.
(莫莉喘气)
(Molly panting)
(莫莉哭泣)
(Molly sobbing)
不!
No!
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(强烈的音乐)
(intense music)
(莫莉喘气)
(Molly panting)
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
(莫莉哭)
(Molly crying)
——对不起,
- I'm sorry,
为了这一切。
for all of it.
(紧张的音乐)
(tense music)
-尽你所能盯着看?
- Stare all you can do?
-我应该看着你的
- I'm supposed to watch ya.
Chisos这样说的。
Chisos said so.
-你知道盯着看和看不是一回事。
- You know staring and watching aren't the same thing.
我感觉到你在盯着一个强大的东西。
And I feel you staring something powerful.
是的。
Yeah.
像货运火车一样强大。
Powerful like a freight train.
你介意我叫你货运火车吗?
Do you mind if I call you Freight Train?
-你想要什么都行
- Whatever you want,
我只是来做我该做的。
I'm just here doing what I'm supposed to.
-我之前感觉到他们的手在摸我
- You know, I felt them hands on me earlier,
超过了必要的长度，
longer than was strictly necessary,
他们也觉得自己很强大。
and they felt powerful, too.
但温柔。
But gentle.
你内心深处是个温柔的家伙吗?
You a gentle fella deep down?
-不是和女人。
- Not with ladies.
我不是故意的，但是，
I don't mean to be, but,
我一激动，就会粗暴地对待他们。
I get excited, handle 'em too rough.
他们带我来的每个人，包括我妻子，
Everyone they brought me, even my wife,
把她抓得太紧了。
got a hold of her too hard.
现在她的气管不能正常工作。
Now her windpipe don't work right.
现在我再也不碰她了。
Shy's away from me touching her at all now.
-你知道的，当你习惯了粗暴并没有那么糟糕。
- Well you know, rough ain't so bad when you're used to it.
事实上，粗糙造就了一些女孩
In fact, rough makes some girls
比庞恰特雷恩河还湿。
wetter than the Pontchartrain.
你能保守秘密吗?
Can you keep a secret?
我是其中一个女孩，
I'm one of them girls,
在他们手里我什么都感觉不到
and I ain't felt nothing in them hands
我发现自己并不需要
that I don't find myself wanting,
我觉得你也想要
and I think you want it, too.
他们对我百般呵护。
Them hands all over me.
(玛格达低声呻吟)
(Magda whimpers)
我不是想骗你出去。
I ain't trying to trick you to get out.
如果你愿意，你甚至可以进来。
Hell, you could even come in here if you wanted to.
我要好好抚摸你。
I gotta touch you proper.
拜托，你不能就这样把我弄出来然后又否定我。
Come on, you can't get me out like this then deny me.
-奇索斯不会容忍的。
- Chisos wouldn't stand for it.
-去他的奶酪酱。
- Fuck Cheese Sauce.
饼干(笑)
(Cookie laughs)
再说了，我以为我们在保守秘密。
Besides, I thought we was keeping secrets.
你知道，这是一个永远不会说出去的秘密
You know, it's a secret that's never told
这提供了最不寻常的悬念。
that offers the most extraordinary of suspense.
我不知道你们怎么想
And I don't know about you,
但我不会告诉任何人的
but I ain't gonna tell a soul.
嘘。
Shh.
(光戏剧性的音乐)
(light dramatic music)
-把腿伸出来。
- Stick your leg out.
-好吧，我会照你说的做
- Okay, I'll do what you say,
但等我出去了，你也得听我的。
but then when I get out, you gotta do what I say, too.
取笑会让取悦变得更好。
Teasing makes the pleasing so much better.
一旦你把那东西固定好，就坐下，好吗?
Once you get that thing fastened, sit down, okay?
来吧，坐下。
Go on, sit down now.
我得从桌子上挪开点
Gonna have to scooch away from that table
如果你想让我坐在你腿上。
if you want me to sit in your lap.
(光悬疑的音乐)
(light suspenseful music)
-我要你知道我是个信教的人。
- I need you to know that I'm a religious man.
我是。
I am.
我相信，
I do believe in, in,
通过消灭罪恶来背负这个世界的重量。
in carrying the weight of the world by consuming sin.
我喜欢，我就是喜欢。
I do, I just do.
(口吃)即使你们这些人认为我们疯了什么的。
(stuttering) even if you people think we's crazy and all.
-不，没人觉得你疯了
- No, nobody thinks you're crazy.
没人觉得你疯了。
Nobody thinks you're crazy.
-只是，我，我，我，我
- It's just, I, I, I, I,
我找不到你做错的事。
I can't find nothing wrong ya done.
-就像我说的，没事，没事。
- Like I said, nothing's wrong, nothing's wrong.
没有人什么也没做。
Nobody did nothing.
-如果你犯了什么罪。
- If you'd have done some sinning.
-没人什么都没做。
- [Frank] Nobody did nothing.
-我没有问题。
- I'd a had no issue.
-你得帮帮我。
- Just gotta help me.
帮我出去。
Help me outta here.
听着，给我扔根绳子。
Look, just, just throw me a rope.
-不不不-不不不
- No, no, no. - No, no, no.
你要做的就是-
All you gotta do is-
-不，不，闭嘴。-请帮帮我们。
- No, no, shut your mouth. - Help us, please.
闭上你的臭嘴!
- Just shut your fuckin' mouth!
Shut your fuckin' mouth!
马上把它关上!
Just shut it, now!
我不会为了救你而出卖自己人，
I ain't gonna save you and cross my own people,
但是你可以拯救你自己。
but you can save yourself.
-你在说什么?
- What are you talking about?
(结结巴巴地)你在说什么?
(stuttering) What are you talking about?
-你得像我一样犯罪才行。
- You gonna have to commit a sin just like me to do it.
-你在说什么?
- What are you talking about?
(强烈的音乐)
(intense music)
他妈的?
The fuck?
上帝!
God!
(强烈的音乐)
(intense music)
(监视器哔哔声)(激烈的音乐)
(monitor beeping) (intense music)
-没有孩子，没有。
- No child, no.
(除颤器啸声)
(defibrillator squealing)
(除颤器震惊)
(defibrillator shocking)
祝福你,孩子。
Bless you, child.
我要用今天的死来告诉他你爱他。
I'll tell him you loved him by dying today.
(强烈的音乐)
(intense music)
(除颤器啸声)
(defibrillator squealing)
(除颤器震惊)
(defibrillator shocking)
你还在外面，不是吗?
You're still out, ain't you?
(强烈的音乐)
(intense music)
你让爱永存。
You keep that love alive.
听到了吗，孩子?
You hear me, child?
你抓紧了。
You hold on tight.
永远不要放弃。
Don't ever let it go.
(强烈的音乐)
(intense music)
(光戏剧性的音乐)
(light dramatic music)
——挪。
- Scooch.
-你到那个角落去，转过身去。
- You get in that corner and turn around.
这可不是妻子该看的。
This ain't a wifely thing to watch.
(玛格达呜咽)
(Magda whimpering)
——Uh-uh-uh。
- Uh-uh-uh.
先戏弄，后取悦。
Teasin' first, pleasin' second.
给你。
Here you go.
只是看。
Just look.
你以前从没见过这样的东西，对吧?
You never laid eyes on anything like this before, have you?
准备好了吗，货运列车?
You ready, Freight Train?
告诉我。
Tell me.
我准备好了。
- I'm ready.
-不，看着我告诉我。
- No, look at me and tell me.
我准备好了。
- I'm ready.
-如果你见到他，告诉他我为过去的事感到抱歉。
- If you meet him, tell him I'm sorry about the past.
(激烈的音乐)(饼干尖叫)
(intense music) (Cookie screaming)
(鸟叫声)
(bird squawking)
(戏剧性的音乐)
(dramatic music)
(饼干的)
(Cookie grunting)
“内洛普，我来了!”
- 'Nelope, I'm coming!
(佩内洛普尖叫)(饼干嘟囔)
(Penelope screaming) (Cookie grunting)
(戏剧性的音乐)
(dramatic music)
(激烈的音乐)(饼干尖叫)
(intense music) (Cookie screaming)
弗兰克,弗兰克!
- Frank, Frank!
该死的，弗兰克!
Oh God damn it, Frank!
——“Nelope !
- 'Nelope!
-[佩内洛普]弗兰克，弗兰克!
- [Penelope] Frank, Frank!
弗兰克，我够不着钥匙!
Frank, I can't reach the keys!
(强烈的音乐)
(intense music)
“内洛普，我们离开这里吧!”
- 'Nelope, let's get outta here!
(弗兰克大喊)(饼干尖叫)
(Frank yelling) (Cookie screaming)
“内洛普，快上车!”
'Nelope get to the car!
“内洛普，滚出去!”
'Nelope, get outta here!
(头骨处理)
(skull crunching)
(电话响了)
(phone ringing)
——“Nelope !弗兰克,弗兰克!
- 'Nelope! - Frank, Frank!
-[弗兰克]快离开这里!
- [Frank] Gotta get outta here!
弗兰克，帮我拿钥匙!
- [Penelope] Frank, help me grab the keys!
-“Nelope，快离开这里!”
- [Frank] 'Nelope, just get outta here!
-[佩内洛普]弗兰克，弗兰克!
- [Penelope] Frank, Frank!
(弗兰克)——“Nelope !
- [Frank] 'Nelope!
弗兰克，我来了，我来了!
- Frank, I'm coming, I'm coming!
-[弗兰克]快上车!
- [Frank] Get to the car!
(弗兰克嘟囔着)(激烈的音乐)
(Frank grunting) (intense music)
(玛格达呜咽)
(Magda whimpering)
——弗兰克!
- Frank!
(令人难以忘怀的音乐)
(haunting music)
-左，左，左。
- Left, left, left.
一个男孩。
That a boy.
(和平的音乐)
(peaceful music)
♪我们有两个♪
♪ There are two of us ♪
-天啊。
- Oh my God.
——这混蛋。
- This motherfucker.
♬走得这么快，我们所有的怀疑都被解开了
♪ Going so fast every doubt we had is coming undone ♪
-货运火车，对吧，伙计?
- Freight train, huh, buddy?
我们将会看到。
We'll see.
(发动机)
(engine dying)
♪太久了♪
♪ For far too long ♪
(引擎窒息)
(engine choking)
-天啊。
- Oh my God.
他来了。
Here he comes.
-今天不行，伙计
- Oh, not today, buddy.
♬他们可以来我希望有人告诉他们
♪ They could come along I wish they'd been told ♪
(引擎窒息)
(engine choking)
——等待,等待。
- Wait, wait.
-宝贝，你在干什么?
- Baby, what are you doing?
♪我们知道什么♪
♪ What we know ♪
♬也不是没有过
♪ It's not unheard of ♪
-努力，努力，努力。
- Try, try, try.
(引擎点击)
(engine clicking)
——不,宝贝。
- No, baby.
(发动机启动)
(engine starting)
(弗兰克喘气)
(Frank panting)
来吧,宝贝。
Come on, baby.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
(轮胎尖叫)
(tires screeching)
这混蛋!
This motherfucker!
(弗兰克嘟哝)
(Frank grunting)
最后一秒让这混蛋看!
One last second for this motherfucker to see!
(弗兰克大叫)
(Frank yelling)
(身体崩溃)(佩内洛普尖叫)
(body crashing) (Penelope screams)
(弗兰克大叫)
(Frank yelling)
(佩内洛普·尖叫)
(Penelope screaming)
(身体扑扑的)
(body thudding)
-他在车下面!
- He's under the car!
(弗兰克嘟哝)
(Frank grunting)
该死的货运火车!
Freight train my fucking ass!
操你，操你，操你!
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you!
-没事了，宝贝，没事了，没事了，没事了
- It's okay, baby, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
♪自己现在♪
♪ Selves now ♪
(光欢快的音乐)
(light upbeat music)
♬没有赛跑，只有奔跑的人
♪ There's no race there's only a runner ♪
♪只要让一只脚一直走到另一只脚
♪ Just keep one foot in front of the other ♪
♬没有赛跑，只有奔跑的人，哦哦♬
♪ There's no race there's only a runner, oh oh ♪
♪一，二，三，即使你累了
♪ One, two, three, even when you get tired ♪
♪只要让一只脚一直走到另一只脚
♪ Just keep one foot in front of the other ♪
(莫莉尿)
(Molly peeing)
♬没有比赛，没有终点
♪ There's no race no ending in sight ♪
♪没有秒太短没有窗太紧
♪ No second too short no window too tight ♪
♪离开的时候把灯关掉♪
♪ Turn off the lights when you leave ♪
♪因为我们已经有了需要的一切♪
♪ 'Cause we got everything we're gonna need ♪
(Chisos呻吟)
(Chisos moaning)
♬我们在逃跑，我们在逃跑，我们在逃跑的子♬
♪ We're on the run, we're on the run, we're on the run child ♪
(枪击发)
(gun cocking)
♬我们要跑，我们要跑，我们要跑，孩子♬
♪ We gotta run, we gotta run, we gotta run child ♪
(枪声解雇)
(gunshots firing)
总有一天我们会告诉♬
♪ One day we tell ♪
♪我们的故事♪
♪ Our story of ♪
♬我们怎么做♬
♪ How we made something ♪
♪我们为自己做了些什么♪
♪ We made something of ourselves ♪
——嘿,
- Hey,
我知道他们会在电影的最后翻越悬崖，
I know that they go over a cliff at the end of the movie,
“塞尔玛和露易丝。”
"Thelma & Louise."
-那条路很难看，
- That road was ugly,
它不适合我们的任何一辆车。
and it wasn't fit for any car of ours.
而且，我们现在的方向不同了，宝贝。
Besides, we're going in a different direction now, baby.
-请不要进去
- Please don't go in there.
求你了，我们想要什么都可以去买。
Please, whatever we need we can go get.
我们可以去别的地方买。
We can get it somewhere else.
-我马上就回来。
- I'll just be back in a sec.
-拜托，我很害怕。
- Please, I'm scared.
我真的很害怕，如果你走了，如果你离开，
I'm really scared that if you go, if you leave,
你会看到她的。
you're gonna see her.
你会。-别这样
You're gonna- - Don't be.
我回来了。
I'm coming back.
——我知道。
- I know.
他们只是单词。
They're just words.
我以前听过。
I've heard 'em before.
-不，你没有。
- No, you haven't.
这是我说的话，我说的话。
Those are my words, my words.
我马上回来。
And I'm coming back.
♬你知道我需要你的爱
♪ You know I need your love ♪
♪你已经控制了我♪
♪ You've got that hold over me ♪
♪只要有你的爱♪
♪ Long as I've got your love ♪
♪你知道我永远不会离开♪
♪ You know that I'll never leave ♪
♪当我想和你分享我的生活♪
♪ When I wanted you to share my life ♪
——没有。
- No.
-你根本不关心他。
- You don't give a shit about him.
-给我滚。-你不可能。
- Get the fuck outta here. - You can't possibly.
-你在这里干什么?
- What are you doing here?
我告诉过你我们结束了。
I told you that we're over.
-你喊了我的名字好几个月了
- You were screaming my name for months.
-滚出去，马上。
- Get out of here, right now.
认真对待。-真想吐。
Seriously. - Gagging for it.
-滚出我的地盘!
- Get the fuck off of my property!
走吧!
Go!
请弗兰克,弗兰克。
Frank, Frank, please.
——那?
- That?
那是你的丈夫吗?
That's your husband?
那就是你要和他住在一起的人
That's who you're staying with
在我把你掏空之后?
after I hollowed you the fuck out?
很好。
Fine.
也许我该把它掏空。
Maybe I should start hollowing that out.
♪我经历的改变♪
♪ Changes that I've been through ♪
♬他们在我身上留下了印记
♪ They've left a mark on me ♪
♬你就像北极星一样永恒
♪ You've been as constant as a Northern star ♪
——什么?
- What?
我训练过终极格斗冠军赛，混蛋。
I trained UFC, motherfucker.
把它,婊子!
Bring it, bitch!
(弗兰克嘟哝)
(Frank grunting)
哇，哇，嘿，伙计。
Whoa, whoa, hey man.
哇,哇,男人。
Whoa, whoa, man.
(人的)
(man grunting)
——不!-天啊，不!
- No! - Oh God, no!
(弗兰克嘟囔着)(骨头嘎吱作响)
(Frank grunting) (bone crunching)
♪只想说这是我的路♪
♪ Just wanna say this is my way ♪
♪告诉你一切♪
♪ Of telling you everything ♪
请- - - - - -弗兰克。
- Frank, please.
拜托!
Please!
宝贝,请,谢谢!
Baby, please, please!
弗兰克。(哭)
Frank. (crying)
对，这就是我的路
♪ Yeah this is my way ♪
弗兰克。(哭)
Frank. (crying)
♪每天告诉你♪
♪ Of telling you that everyday ♪
宝贝,请!(哭泣)
Baby, please! (sobbing)
♬我更爱你了
♪ I'm loving you so much more ♪
♪因为你相信我♪
♪ 'Cause you believed in me ♪
宝贝,请!
Baby, please!
♬穿过我最黑暗的夜晚
♪ Through my darkest night ♪
♪让我拥有更好的自己
♪ Put something better inside of me ♪
♪你把我带到了光里
♪ You brought me into the light ♪
♪扔掉所有那些疯狂的梦想♪
♪ Threw away all those crazy dreams ♪
♪我把它们都抛在身后
♪ I put them all behind ♪
-那是愤怒。
- That was rage.
真正的愤怒。
Real rage.
没关系的，你知道吗?
Well, it's okay, you know?
我们没买到衣服也没关系
It's okay that we didn't get any the clothes
或者任何你需要的东西
or anything you needed
因为我们可以去沃尔玛买
because we can just stop at Walmart and get-
——嘘。
- Shh.
♪只想说这是我的路♪
♪ Just wanna say this is my way ♪
我得到了我想要的。
I got exactly what I came for.
我还有一个问题。
And I got one more question.
你会穿吗?
Will you wear it?
对，这就是我的路
♪ Yeah this is my way ♪
♪告诉你每一天我都爱你♪
♪ Telling you that everyday I'm loving you ♪
-是的，是的，是的。
- Yes, yes, yes.
我会的，而且我永远不会脱下来。
I, I will, and I'll never take it off.
♪如果我节节败退♪
♪ If I'm losing ground ♪
我爱你，弗兰克。
I love you, Frank.
-我爱你，内洛普。
- I love you, 'Nelope.
我对上帝发誓，内洛普，
I swear to God, 'Nelope,
你是彩虹尽头的女孩。
you're the girl at the end of the rainbow.
♪一直都是你，女人，一直都是你
♪ It's been you, woman, right down the line ♪
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
-是的，我现在就在盯着他们
- Yeah, I got an eye on 'em right now,
因为没人偷我的东西。
'cause nobody fuckin' steals from me.
(用外语)
(speaking in foreign language)
(引擎的转速)
(engine revving)
(不祥的音乐)
(ominous music)
-(歌手)一、二、三。
- [Singer] One, two, three.
♪你从来没有♪
♪ Don't you ever ♪
♪伤心♪
♪ Be sad ♪
♪靠在我身上♪
♪ Oh lean on me ♪
♬当时代变坏的时候
♪ When the times get bad ♪
♬当我们的那一天到来的时候
♪ When our day comes ♪
♬你被打倒了♬
♪ And you are down ♪
♪在麻烦的河流里♪
♪ In a river of trouble ♪
♬就要被淹死了
♪ About to drown ♪
♪好吧，只要坚持♬
♪ Well just hold on ♪
♬我来了♬
♪ I'm coming ♪
♪只要坚持♬
♪ Just hold on ♪
♬我来了♬
♪ I'm coming ♪
♬我在我的路上
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♬你的爱♬
♪ Your love ♪
♪哦当你冷的时候♪
♪ Ooh when you get cold ♪
♪我将是你的掩护♪
♪ I'll be your cover ♪
♪你不用担心♪
♪ You don't have to worry ♪
♪因为我在这里♪
♪ Because I'm here ♪
♪我不需要承受♪
♪ I don't need to suffer ♪
♬因为我在♬附近
♪ Because I'm near ♪
♪只要坚持♬
♪ Just hold on ♪
♬我来了♬
♪ I'm comin' ♪
♬按住♬
♪ Hold on ♪
对，我来了
♪ Yeah I'm comin' ♪
♬按住♬
♪ Hold on ♪
♬我来了♬
♪ I'm comin' ♪
♪哦，坚持住♬
♪ Ooh hold on ♪
♪我来了，是啊♪
♪ I'm comin', yeah ♪
♬靠近我就行了♬
♪ Just reach out to me ♪
♬为了满足♬
♪ For satisfaction ♪
♪只要叫我的名字♪
♪ Oh just call my name ♪
♬为了快速反应♬
♪ For quick reaction ♪
是的♪♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪哦，你永远不会♪
♪ Oh don't you ever ♪
♪你永远不要悲伤
♪ Don't you ever be sad ♪
♪你能不能依靠我♪
♪ Won't you lean on me ♪
♬当他们的时代变得糟糕的时候
♪ When them times get bad ♪
♪哦，当那一天来临♪
♪ Oh when the day comes ♪
♪哦，你倒下了♪
♪ Oh and you are down ♪
♬你在一条麻烦的河里
♪ You're in a river of trouble ♪
♬你就要被淹死了
♪ You're about to drown ♪
♪哦，坚持住♪
♪ Oh, hold on ♪
♬我来了♬
♪ I'm comin' ♪
♪只要坚持♬
♪ Just hold on ♪
♬亲爱的，我来了
♪ Darlin' I'm comin' ♪
♪只要坚持♬
♪ Just hold on ♪
♬我来了♬
♪ I'm comin' ♪
♪你不会坚持♪
♪ Won't cha hold on ♪
♬哦，我来了♬
♪ Ooh I'm comin' ♪
♬按住♬
♪ Hold on ♪
♬我来了♬
♪ I'm comin' ♪
♪只要坚持♬
♪ Just hold on ♪
♬我来了♬
♪ I'm comin' ♪
♪只要坚持♬
♪ Just hold on ♪
♬我来了♬
♪ I'm comin' ♪